<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<?xml-stylesheet href="/assets/styles.xslt" type="text/xml"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/feeds/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <title>Bechno Kid&#39;s Hideout - RSS Feed</title>
    <link>https://bechnokid.neocities.org</link>
    <description>The latest (and greatest?) from a beet disguised as a masked humanoid entity.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <docs>https://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <item>
      <title>Feb 7, 2026</title>
      <link>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">update-Fri Feb 06 2026 19:00:00 GMT-0500 (Eastern Standard Time)</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>Whoa, two updates in a week? It's almost unheard of!</p>
<p>Here's what's in today's update!</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/tutorials/rss-feed">New tutorial</a>! This one is for adding full descriptions to &quot;prettified&quot; RSS Feeds.</li>
<li>The old <a href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/guestbook">guestbook</a> has returned! Yippee!!</li>
<li>Added a section for <a href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/joined">pending webrings</a>.</li>
<li>Other fixes such as:
<ul>
<li>Reorganizing and cleaning up a lot of pages</li>
<li>Culling some of the quiz results and putting them in my <a href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/about">/about</a> page.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>That's it for now! I hope all of you have a great day!</p>
        ]]></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feb 5, 2026</title>
      <link>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">update-Wed Feb 04 2026 19:00:00 GMT-0500 (Eastern Standard Time)</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>Hello, everyone! I hope things are going ok for all of you! It's still pretty cold, but I hear that it'll get warmer next week! Just in time for my birthday!</p>
<p>Here's what's new in this update!</p>
<ul>
<li>I moved the light/dark toggle button to be positioned below the navigation sidebar! I figured this might be easier to access since the sidebar is always fixed in one position.</li>
<li>New art in the <a href="/art/anime">anime</a> section!</li>
<li>Added a new <a href="/resources/code-snippets">code snippet</a>. I think Tumblr veterans might recognize this one. 😉</li>
<li>Updated <a href="/now">now</a> and <a href="/goodies/pixel-clubs">pixel club</a> pages!</li>
<li>I will also mention that I also added in new links, but seeing as how I seem to <em>always</em> add in new links with every update, I figure I won't announce it this time. 😅</li>
</ul>
<p>That's it for now. See you next time!</p>
        ]]></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jan 29, 2026</title>
      <link>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">update-Wed Jan 28 2026 19:00:00 GMT-0500 (Eastern Standard Time)</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>Hello everyone! I hope you are all doing well. We all experienced a pretty nasty cold front over here in the East Coast, which makes me all the more grateful that I've been working from home. I hope you are all staying warm this winter!</p>
<p>Here are the latest updates!</p>
<ul>
<li>New art in the <a href="/art/anime">Anime</a> and <a href="/art/other">Other</a> sections!</li>
<li>Lots of new goodies, including:
<ul>
<li>Two more <a href="/goodies/pocket-bishies">Pocket Bishounen</a> quizzes to take.</li>
<li>Lots of graphics I <a href="/goodies/adopts">adopted</a></li>
<li>Some graphics I collected for <a href="/goodies/pixel-clubs">pixel clubs</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Added more <a href="/links">links</a>! One day, I'll be brave and ask some of these new sites to be  affiliates! One day!</li>
<li>Various bug fixes and minor updates</li>
</ul>
<p>That's it for now! I hope you all of a wonderful day!</p>
        ]]></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jan 15, 2026</title>
      <link>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">update-Wed Jan 14 2026 19:00:00 GMT-0500 (Eastern Standard Time)</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>Happy New Year everyone! Today is also the day that the long-awaited version 3.0 of Animal Crossing New Horizons is released! I hope everyone has fun with it.</p>
<p>There are some pretty big updates today:</p>
<ul>
<li>New artwork in the <a href="/art/game">Games</a> section! This is technically a crossover piece, but I don't have enough to make a new section yet lol</li>
<li>New page: <a href="/me/fan">Fangirling</a>, a page that's just me rambling about my experiences and preferences as a fan of media!</li>
<li><a href="/resources/status-cafe/themes">Status Cafe themes</a>:
<ul>
<li>Did a huge rehaul by improving how a theme is previewed and installing a button that will copy the code to your clipboard, making it easy to just paste it into the text box for the <strong>About</strong> section,</li>
<li>Added a new theme! Those from Neocities in 2022-2023 might recognize it lol. I'm being a little shameless with this one hehe.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Added some more links! The more links I move from my bookmarks to this page, the more cool websites I keep finding. This is what I love about the indie web hehe.</li>
</ul>
<p>That's it for now. I hope everyone has a great day!</p>
        ]]></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dec 30, 2025</title>
      <link>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">update-Mon Dec 29 2025 19:00:00 GMT-0500 (Eastern Standard Time)</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>Hi everyone! I hope everyone has had a good time during the winter holidays. This will be the last update for the year. :D</p>
<p>There are so many changes in this update that I'm not sure if I can put them all in this single entry without it being too overwhelming. XD</p>
<p>So, I'll list the most important ones (to me)!</p>
<ul>
<li>New artwork in the <a href="/art/digimon">Digimon</a> section</li>
<li>Made a <a href="/to-do">to-do</a> list for the site</li>
<li>Added two <a href="/links">links</a></li>
<li>Meadow's guestbook service is currently down, so I linked to my <a href="https://bechnokid.atabook.org/">atabook</a> instead. Hopefully it gets fixed soon!</li>
<li>Optimization updates (hopefully):
<ul>
<li>Consolidated most of my JS files into one</li>
<li>Fixed up JS for webrings page</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
        ]]></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dec 8, 2025</title>
      <link>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">update-Sun Dec 07 2025 19:00:00 GMT-0500 (Eastern Standard Time)</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>Hi everyone! It's another cold day in December. We actually had one snow day here! We sadly haven't had snow since then, but I'm holding out hop that it will snow on Christmas!</p>
<p>This update seems pretty small, but that's because most of the updates were on the back end! However, an update is still an update!</p>
<p>Here are the latest changes:</p>
<ul>
<li>Added new clique: <a href="https://crystallizing.neocities.org">Crystallizing</a>. Yes, I chose that gem specifically because of that one animanga, teehee.</li>
<li>Updated <a href="/feeds">RSS</a> and made into page that holds other feeds</li>
<li>Cosmetic updates including:
<ul>
<li>Unifying colors, especially colors for links</li>
<li>Updated <a href="/not_found">404 page</a> image to better match my current look</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Backend updates and fixes including:
<ul>
<li>Minifying and bundling CSS for optimization (hopefully the CSS is still readable to use as reference!)</li>
<li>Updated CSS and JS code for Freezeframe script thanks to <a href="https://friendshaped.garden">FriendShapedPlant</a>!</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>That's it for now! See you next time!</p>
        ]]></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nov 28, 2025</title>
      <link>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">update-Thu Nov 27 2025 19:00:00 GMT-0500 (Eastern Standard Time)</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>Hi everyone! I had a great Thanksgiving and a peaceful Black Friday. Looking forward to the winter holidays now!</p>
<p>Here's what's in this joyous update!</p>
<section>
<h4 id="major-updates" tabindex="-1">Major Updates</h4>
<ul>
<li>New artwork in <a href="/art/digimon">Digimon</a></li>
<li><a href="/resources/tutorials/freezeframe">FreezeframeJS tutorial</a>:
<ul>
<li>Created a new script</li>
<li>Completely rewrote the tutorial on how to use the new script</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><a href="/outgoing/webgarden">Webgarden</a>:
<ul>
<li>Added more pots</li>
<li>Slightly updated the layout so I can fit more pots</li>
<li>Minor revamp of my own web garden pot. I noticed the spacing would look off in some other's sites, oops.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><a href="/links">Links</a>:
<ul>
<li>Added more links</li>
<li>Added some sections</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Removed FreezeframeJS script and added my own</li>
</ul>
</section>
<section>
<h4 id="minor-updates" tabindex="-1">Minor Updates</h4>
<ul>
<li><a href="/about">About Me</a> page:
<ul>
<li>Added more favorite Digimon</li>
<li>Replaced static Digimon images with moving ones</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><a href="/resources/code-snippets">Code Snippets</a> page:
<ul>
<li>Added some CSS to allow users to pause the marquee</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Fixed the <a href="/guestbook">Guestbook</a>. I didn't realize it wasn't displaying all of the messages, which I deeply apologize for!</li>
<li>Other updates and fixes such as:
<ul>
<li>Removed the reliance on margins between items (as much as I can) and replacing them with the <code>gap</code> property used in grids and flex boxes.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>That's it for now! I hope the holidays don't become stressful to you! You can do it!</p>
</section>
        ]]></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>