<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<?xml-stylesheet href="/assets/stylesheets/styles.xslt" type="text/xml"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-US">
  <title>Bechno Kid&#39;s Hideout - Web Feed</title>
  <link href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <subtitle>The latest (and greatest?) from a beet disguised as a software engineer.</subtitle>
  <updated>2025-09-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <id>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/feed.xml</id>
  <author>
    <name>Bechno Kid&#39;s Hideout</name>
    <uri>https://bechnokid.neocities.org</uri>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Nov 5, 2025 </title>
    <link href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home"/>
    <updated>2025-11-05T16:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello, everyone! I hope all of you are doing alright and that seasonal depression has passed for you. If not, then you can do it! I believe in you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s gotten colder, but thankfully I like colder weather! It means I can bundle up, wear my longer coats, and look like a real anime protagonist! Ok, not really...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are the changes for this update!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New artwork in the &lt;a href=&quot;/art/digimon&quot;&gt;Digimon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;/art/anime&quot;&gt;Anime&lt;/a&gt; sections&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added a section with my currently active social media accounts in &lt;a href=&quot;/links&quot;&gt;Links&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New &lt;a href=&quot;/blog&quot;&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt; entry where I talk about my grievances with sites that repost graphics without giving credit to the original artists&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finally decided to join more &lt;a href=&quot;/joined&quot;&gt;fanlistings&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cosmetic updates including:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updating the dark mode colors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adding an icon after external links as well as changing the text color&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Figuring out how to add line numbers to code blocks for future snippets. This will help in pointing specific lines in any code I share!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Moving the Play/Stop GIFs buttons to the navigation bar for easier access&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating a section dedicated to links that don&#39;t have buttons. I encourage others to visit those links!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s it for now. See you all next time!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Oct 27, 2025 </title>
    <link href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home"/>
    <updated>2025-10-27T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s almost Halloween!! I don&#39;t even have any special plans! I just love the holiday that much!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The list of updates is small this time. :3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added three &lt;a href=&quot;/quiz-results&quot;&gt;quiz results&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated &lt;a href=&quot;/now&quot;&gt;/now&lt;/a&gt; and also added a section for older entries! Huge thanks to &lt;a href=&quot;https://mavisdeluna.art&quot;&gt;Mavis&lt;/a&gt; for the idea!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other fixes and updates including:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adding a loading screen to the &lt;a href=&quot;/outgoing/webgarden&quot;&gt;Webgarden&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the styling for &amp;lt;h3&amp;gt; tags to be underlined in almost every page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Oct 21, 2025 </title>
    <link href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home"/>
    <updated>2025-10-21T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Happy &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.playstation.com/2025/10/20/festival-of-accord-dreamspell-comes-to-monster-hunter-wilds-starting-october-22/&quot;&gt;Dreamspell Festival&lt;/a&gt; Eve! I honestly wish I would make more of a habit uploading my art here as soon as I finish drawing it, but I love making updates to the site as well! &lt;img class=&#39;inline-img&#39; src=&#39;/assets/images/blog/emoticon/emote_happy.png&#39; aria-hidden=&#39;true&#39; alt=&#39;&#39;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are the spooky changes for this update:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New artwork in the &lt;a href=&quot;/art/digimon&quot;&gt;Digimon&lt;/a&gt; section&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added a new &lt;a href=&quot;/links&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added back the &lt;a href=&quot;/resources/code-snippets&quot;&gt;code snippets&lt;/a&gt; page! The old snippets are no longer there, but there are some new ones! Check them out if you&#39;d like! I&#39;m hoping to update this a little more frequently!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;/goodies/pixel_clubs&quot;&gt;pixel club&lt;/a&gt; page got a revamp for easier viewing, and I added the Bottlecaps pixel club!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added some &lt;a href=&quot;/goodies/graphics&quot;&gt;honeycomb stamp&lt;/a&gt; graphics! I had been meaning to add them for a while, but making the CSS took a little bit of work!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cosmetic updates and other fixes, including:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added a loading screen to graphic-heavy pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I removed most of the &lt;i class=&#39;ft-alert-triangle index&#39;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; icons as a result, but only if JS is enabled! They are still there if JS is disabled!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added &lt;a href=&quot;/sitemap&quot;&gt;sitemap&lt;/a&gt; to the navigation sidebar for easier access&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s it for now! See you later, and I hope everyone has a great Halloween in 10 days!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Oct 2, 2025 </title>
    <link href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home"/>
    <updated>2025-10-02T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It is the Spooky Month!! Halloween is upon us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some creepy changes for this update:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New artwork in the &lt;a href=&quot;/art/digimon&quot;&gt;Digimon&lt;/a&gt; section&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New &lt;a href=&quot;/writing/blog&quot;&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt; entry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added a clique and &lt;a href=&quot;/links&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New items in all &lt;a href=&quot;/goodies&quot;&gt;Goodies&lt;/a&gt; pages (except for Pocket Bishies) and &lt;a href=&quot;/quiz_results&quot;&gt;Quiz Results&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made some updates to the &lt;a href=&quot;/joined&quot;&gt;webrings&lt;/a&gt; as well as the &lt;a href=&quot;/about&quot;&gt;About&lt;/a&gt; page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other updates and fixes including cosmetic and backend changes, such as:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There should be few to no boxes that have a scroll bar now that I have a &amp;quot;Back to Top&amp;quot; button&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed spacing in a lot of elements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overall, if you don&#39;t notice a lot of differences, that&#39;s a good thing!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s it for now! See you later!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Sep 14, 2025 </title>
    <link href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home"/>
    <updated>2025-09-14T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s finally gotten a little cooler!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You know, I can never decide if I like fall or winter better. I always seem to flip-flop between the two. I just like colder weather in general! Not that I can tolerate the cold, but rather, I like to bundle up and wear lots of layers since I never like to show my skin much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&#39;s what&#39;s in this update!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New page: &lt;a href=&quot;/pocket_bishies&quot;&gt;Pocket Bishies&lt;/a&gt;!
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&#39;ve seen it around, but I never really made a page until now! The collection might stay small since I&#39;m not a huge nerd and the original sites have long stopped working/updating. It is what it is!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you have JavaScript enabled, you can take a few quizzes to nab some bishies of your own! I won&#39;t be taking submissions like the original sites did, but I still hope you enjoy them!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New art in the &lt;a href=&quot;/art/ff&quot;&gt;Final Fantasy&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;/art/digimon&quot;&gt;Digimon&lt;/a&gt; sections!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added 4 &lt;a href=&quot;/goodies/adopts&quot;&gt;adopts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some front-end and back-end fixes, including:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made the guestbook form more accessible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the main page to resize itself automatically if certain parts of the navigation are opened. It isn&#39;t perfect since I want to avoid using JavaScript in the navigation, but it looks pretty good!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shortened the links for art, changing them from &amp;quot;artwork&amp;quot; to &amp;quot;art&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated &lt;a href=&quot;/joined&quot;&gt;Webrings&lt;/a&gt; to use less JavaScript in general. Not sure if I succeeded, but it&#39;s something!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s it for now, see you all next update!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Sep 6, 2025 </title>
    <link href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home"/>
    <updated>2025-09-06T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve been starting to see more shops selling pumpkin spice-flavored snacks, so that means Fall is officially here (I think)!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&#39;s the spice in today&#39;s update!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brought back the &lt;a href=&quot;/quiz_results&quot;&gt;Quiz Results&lt;/a&gt; page! Since I have a lot of space for more images, I thought it&#39;d be nice to bring it back!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed up the installation guide for the &lt;a href=&quot;/resources/status-cafe/themes/dA2006&quot;&gt;deviantART Status Cafe theme&lt;/a&gt;! The tables disappeared in the previous update, so I brought them back!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added two cliques to the home page: &lt;a href=&quot;https://lockheart.love/collections/cliques&quot;&gt;Cutie Connections&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://ac.kuchiki.net/&quot;&gt;pixel friends&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added &lt;a href=&quot;/goodies/adopts&quot;&gt;one adopt&lt;/a&gt; for others to adopt! Admittedly, I didn&#39;t make it. I just revised the colors and other parts of it, but I still love it enough to share!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is now a secret page in the site! Can you find it? :3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Various updates and fixes to help make the site a little bit better, such as adding navigation buttons in some pages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s it for now! See you later!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>