<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<?xml-stylesheet href="/assets/stylesheets/styles.xslt" type="text/xml"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-US">
  <title>Bechno Kid&#39;s Hideout - Web Feed</title>
  <link href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <subtitle>The latest (and greatest?) from a beet disguised as a software engineer.</subtitle>
  <updated>2025-08-06T04:00:00Z</updated>
  <id>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/feed.xml</id>
  <author>
    <name>Bechno Kid&#39;s Hideout</name>
    <uri>https://bechnokid.neocities.org</uri>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Oct 2, 2025 </title>
    <link href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home"/>
    <updated>2025-10-02T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It is the Spooky Month!! Halloween is upon us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some creepy changes for this update:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New artwork in the &lt;a href=&quot;/art/digimon&quot;&gt;Digimon&lt;/a&gt; section&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New &lt;a href=&quot;/writing/blog&quot;&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt; entry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added a clique and &lt;a href=&quot;/links&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New items in all &lt;a href=&quot;/goodies&quot;&gt;Goodies&lt;/a&gt; pages (except for Pocket Bishies) and &lt;a href=&quot;/quiz_results&quot;&gt;Quiz Results&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made some updates to the &lt;a href=&quot;/joined&quot;&gt;webrings&lt;/a&gt; as well as the &lt;a href=&quot;/about&quot;&gt;About&lt;/a&gt; page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other updates and fixes including cosmetic and backend changes, such as:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There should be few to no boxes that have a scroll bar now that I have a &amp;quot;Back to Top&amp;quot; button&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed spacing in a lot of elements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overall, if you don&#39;t notice a lot of differences, that&#39;s a good thing!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s it for now! See you later!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Sep 14, 2025 </title>
    <link href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home"/>
    <updated>2025-09-14T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s finally gotten a little cooler!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You know, I can never decide if I like fall or winter better. I always seem to flip-flop between the two. I just like colder weather in general! Not that I can tolerate the cold, but rather, I like to bundle up and wear lots of layers since I never like to show my skin much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&#39;s what&#39;s in this update!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New page: &lt;a href=&quot;/pocket_bishies&quot;&gt;Pocket Bishies&lt;/a&gt;!
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&#39;ve seen it around, but I never really made a page until now! The collection might stay small since I&#39;m not a huge nerd and the original sites have long stopped working/updating. It is what it is!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you have JavaScript enabled, you can take a few quizzes to nab some bishies of your own! I won&#39;t be taking submissions like the original sites did, but I still hope you enjoy them!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New art in the &lt;a href=&quot;/art/ff&quot;&gt;Final Fantasy&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;/art/digimon&quot;&gt;Digimon&lt;/a&gt; sections!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added 4 &lt;a href=&quot;/goodies/adopts&quot;&gt;adopts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some front-end and back-end fixes, including:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made the guestbook form more accessible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated the main page to resize itself automatically if certain parts of the navigation are opened. It isn&#39;t perfect since I want to avoid using JavaScript in the navigation, but it looks pretty good!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shortened the links for art, changing them from &amp;quot;artwork&amp;quot; to &amp;quot;art&amp;quot;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updated &lt;a href=&quot;/joined&quot;&gt;Webrings&lt;/a&gt; to use less JavaScript in general. Not sure if I succeeded, but it&#39;s something!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s it for now, see you all next update!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Sep 6, 2025 </title>
    <link href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home"/>
    <updated>2025-09-06T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve been starting to see more shops selling pumpkin spice-flavored snacks, so that means Fall is officially here (I think)!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&#39;s the spice in today&#39;s update!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brought back the &lt;a href=&quot;/quiz_results&quot;&gt;Quiz Results&lt;/a&gt; page! Since I have a lot of space for more images, I thought it&#39;d be nice to bring it back!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixed up the installation guide for the &lt;a href=&quot;/resources/status-cafe/themes/dA2006&quot;&gt;deviantART Status Cafe theme&lt;/a&gt;! The tables disappeared in the previous update, so I brought them back!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added two cliques to the home page: &lt;a href=&quot;https://lockheart.love/collections/cliques&quot;&gt;Cutie Connections&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://ac.kuchiki.net/&quot;&gt;pixel friends&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added &lt;a href=&quot;/goodies/adopts&quot;&gt;one adopt&lt;/a&gt; for others to adopt! Admittedly, I didn&#39;t make it. I just revised the colors and other parts of it, but I still love it enough to share!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is now a secret page in the site! Can you find it? :3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Various updates and fixes to help make the site a little bit better, such as adding navigation buttons in some pages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&#39;s it for now! See you later!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Aug 30, 2025 </title>
    <link href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home"/>
    <updated>2025-08-30T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone! It&#39;s almost September, and while the summer weather is still ever-present, I&#39;m looking forward to the cooler weather that Fall brings!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&#39;s what&#39;s in today&#39;s update!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;/artwork&quot;&gt;art gallery&lt;/a&gt; is finally up! I&#39;ll work on adding more before I reach the limit even with a Supporter account!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Had to remove a few broken fanlistings. &lt;img class=&#39;inline-img&#39; src=&#39;/assets/images/blog/emoticon/emote_worried.png&#39; aria-hidden=&#39;true&#39; alt=&#39;&#39;&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rearranged a few webrings as well as &lt;a href=&quot;/joined&quot;&gt;added some new ones&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Aug 13, 2025 </title>
    <link href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home"/>
    <updated>2025-08-13T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hello, everyone! I hope you&#39;ve all been doing well! It hasn&#39;t been too bad, temperature-wise, but that&#39;s because I mostly stay inside. I need to get out more...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The newest updates have a lot to do with webrings!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added &lt;a href=&quot;/joined&quot;&gt;PersonaRing&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All webrings can be viewed even with JavaScript disabled! This involved me making the buttons myself lol.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Webring widgets where I&#39;m a pending member will also have more consistent styling.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other backend fixes for optimization...at least I hope so!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Aug 6, 2025 </title>
    <link href="https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home"/>
    <updated>2025-08-06T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://bechnokid.neocities.org/home</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hi, everyone! It&#39;s almost back to school for some of you! I wish you the best in the school period, whether it&#39;s a year, semester, quarter. You can do it! &lt;img class=&#39;inline-img&#39; src=&#39;/assets/images/blog/emoticon/emote_happy.png&#39; aria-hidden=&#39;true&#39; alt=&#39;&#39;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still progressing through getting my art gallery ready. I managed to get to 2012! It&#39;s...not great, but progress is progress!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are the updates for this site!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created a new section, &lt;a href=&quot;/resources/status-cafe/themes&quot;&gt;Status Cafe Themes&lt;/a&gt;! Not sure if I&#39;ll be able to make more themes or just have the one, but we&#39;ll see!
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Status Cafe Feed Tutorial has also been moved into the same section as the themes. The old links should still work!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added two new cliques to the front page: &lt;a href=&quot;https://fan.sanguineroyal.com/cli/barbieland/&quot;&gt;Barbieland&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://miasma.dual-weekend.com/&quot;&gt;Miasma&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New journal entry, &lt;a href=&quot;/writing/blog/2025-08-06&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;I&#39;m Not an Ideal Asian&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;, where I discuss my desire for a single crumb of representation as a &amp;quot;non-ideal&amp;quot; Asian American.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So many backend fixes, including fixing broken links and other things!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>